

CONTACT

+49 15254706681

✓ tomifarm@hotmail.com

Berlin

tomifarm.github.io/portfolio/

m www.linkedin.com/in/tomifaerm/

TECHNICAL SKILLS

- Java Script
- React JS
- Node JS
- Express
- MongoDB
- Angular
- React Native
- HTML & CSS

ADDITIONAL SKILLS

- Leadership & People Management
- Customer focus
- Service Operations
- Practical Problem-Solving
- Clear Communication
- Data analysis and reporting

LANGUAGE SKILLS

English - professional profiency Finnish - native

German - intermediate

TOMI FÄRM

WEB DEVELOPER

Qualified FS Web Developer with a focus on Java Script, React JS, Node JS, Express, MongoDB stack. Enthusiastic about understanding technologies and drive for learning. Strong team player with an eye for detail and leadership experience in tech.

WORK EXPERIENCE

IT HELPDESK SPECIALIST

akut... HR Consulting GmbH 2020 - 2022

- First level IT support for eBay employees worldwide
- Supporting with all IT related issues and responding employee queries via chat and phone

SERVICE OPERATIONS TEAM LEAD FINLAND

Delivery Hero SE

2018 - 2019

- Team and people management
- Analyzing and reporting of service operations performance
- Upskill training of agents
- Working with various backend, frontend, CRM, HR and management solutions and tools

CUSTOMER AND PARTNER SERVICE AGENT FOR FOODORA

Delivery Hero SE

2017 - 2018

- Solving customers' and partner restaurants' issues and responding queries via chat, phone and email
- Working with various backend, frontend and CRM solutions and tools

Detailed working experience can be found on my Linkedin.

EDUCATION

FULL-STACK WEB DEVELOPMENT PROGRAM

CareerFoundry, 2023

BACHELOR OF HOSPITALITY MANAGEMENT

Tampere University of Applied Sciences, 2012